Robert S. Phillips Papers
Robert S. Phillips Papers
- Writings
  - Books
    - Goyen, William. William Goyen: Selected Letters from a Writer's Life (working title: "Selected Letters of William Goyen") (University of Texas Press, ), 1995
      - Manuscript with Reginald Gibbons' queries, 4 folders (Box 16A)
      - Manuscript "revised 6/93", 4 folders (Box 16A)
      - Manuscript "corrected 12/93", 4 folders (Box 16A)
      - Manuscript on disk (2) (Box 16A)
      - Production records
        - Page proofs, with R. Phillips' corrections, 3 folders (Box 16A)
      - Manuscript, 5 folders (Box 17)
      - Production records
        - Page proofs, 5 folders (Box 17)
    - Inner Weather (Golden Quill Press), 1966
      - Production records
        - Galleys (Box 17)
    - The Land of Lost Content (Vanguard Press), 1970
      - Typescript ms., 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Literary New York (Peregrine Smith Books), 1991
      - Research material, 4 folders (Box 17)
      - Outlines (Box 17)
      - Manuscript (holograph) (Box 17)
      - Manuscript "early version" (Box 17)
      - Manuscript "revised" (Box 17)
      - Introduction, production records (with revisions) (Box 17)
    - Louis L'Amour: His Life and Trails (Paperjacks), 1989
      - Research material, 3 folders (Box 18)
      - Ms. draft, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Manuscript, 3 folders (Box 18)
      - Production records, dust jacket (Box 18)
    - Moonstruck (Vanguard Press), 1974
      - Early draft, deletions, various pagings (Box 18)
      - Introduction, ms. (Box 18)
      - Manuscript, 3 folders (Box 18)
      - Production records
        - Galleys, 5 folders (Box 18)
    - The Passionate Few
      - Manuscript draft, 3 folders (Box 18)
      - Manuscript (Selections, revised), 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Manuscript, 3 folders (Box 18A)
    - Personal Accounts (Ontario Review Press), 1986
      - Typescript ms., 2 folders (Box 18A)
      - Manuscript (Box 18A)
      - Typescript ms., 2 folders (Box 18A)
      - Typescript ms. (3 versions) (Box 18A)
      - Typescript ms. with Dana Gioia commentary (Box 18A)
      - Production records (Box 18A)
    - The Pregnant Man (Doubleday), 1978
      - Typescript ms. of its predecessor "Sea Changes" (Box 19)
      - Typescript ms., 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Typescript ms., 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Typescript ms. (photocopy) (Box 19)
      - Production records
        - Setting copy (Box 19)
        - Galleys, 3 folders (Box 19)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 19)
    - Public Landing Revisited (Story Line Press), 1992
      - Prologue, ms. draft (Box 19)
      - Manuscript (partial) (Box 19)
      - Typescript ms., 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Manuscript (disk printout) (Box 19)
      - Manuscript (disk printout, revised) (Box 19)
    - Running on Empty (Doubleday), 1981
      - Typescript ms., 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Ms. with printer's marks (Box 19)
      - Production records
        - Galleys, 2 folders (Box 19)
        - Page proofs (Box 19)
        - Dust jacket photograph (Box 19)
    - Schwartz, Delmore. Delmore Schwartz and James Laughlin: Selected Letters / edited by R. Phillips (Norton, ), 1993
      - Transcripts, 7 folders (Box 19)
      - Manuscript, 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Manuscript, 5 folders (Box 20)
      - Manuscript (photocopy), 5 folders (Box 20)
      - Manuscript, setting copy; 5 folders (Box 20)
      - Index, manuscript, page proofs (Box 20)
      - Production records
        - Galley proofs, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Page proofs, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Schwartz, Delmore. The Ego Is Always at the Wheel: Bagatelles / edited by R. Phillips (New Directions, ), 1986
      - Manuscript, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Manuscript, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Manuscript (partial) (Box 20)
      - Production records, Galleys (Box 20)
    - Schwartz, Delmore. Last and Lost Poems of Delmore Schwartz / edited by R. Phillips (Vanguard Press, ), 1979
      - Foreword, typescript ms. (Box 21)
      - Manuscript, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Manuscript, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Manuscript, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Production records
        - Galleys (Box 21)
        - Page proofs (Box 21)
    - Schwartz, Delmore. Last & Lost Poems / edited by R. Phillips (New Directions, ), 1989
      - Manuscript, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Schwartz, Delmore. Letters of Delmore Schwartz / edited by R. Phillips (Ontario Review Press, ), 1984
      - Transcripts
        - Schwartz/ Aiken, Conrad (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/ Ames, Elizabeth (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/ Arrowsmith, William (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/ Auden, W. H. (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Barrett, William (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Bellow, Saul (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Berger, Arthur (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Berryman, John (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Blackmur, R. P. (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Buckman, Gertrude (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Cole, William (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Covici, Pascal (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Dike, Donald (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Dillon, George (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Dupee, F. W. (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Goodman, Paul (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Hivnor, Robert (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Horton, Philip (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Jarrell, Randall (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Johnson, Norman (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Langland, Joseph (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Laughlin, James (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Lowell, Robert (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Macdonald, Dwight and Nancy, 2 folders (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Maxwell, William (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Mizener, Arthur (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Moss, Howard (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/New Republic (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Norman, Dorothy (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Palmer, George (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Partisan Review (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Pearson, Norman Holmes (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Pollet, Elizabeth (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Pound, Ezra (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Rago, Henry (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Rahv, Philip (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Ransom, John Crowe (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Rice, Philip Blair (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Sawyer, Julian (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Schapiro, Meyer (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Shapiro, Karl Jay (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Stafford, Jean (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Steloff, Frances (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Stevens, Wallace (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Symons, Julian (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Tate, Allen (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Van Doren, Mark (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Williams, Oscar (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Williams, William Carlos (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/Zolotow, Maurice (Box 21)
        - Schwartz/miscellaneous (Box 21)
      - Deletions, 1931-1962; 3 folders (Box 21)
      - Typescript ms., 10 folders (Box 22)
      - Notes (Box 22)
      - Typescript ms., 8 folders (Box 22)
      - Footnotes (Box 22)
      - Production records
        - Galleys, 4 folders (Box 22)
        - Miscellany (Box 22)
    - Schwartz, Delmore. Shenandoah and Other Verse Plays / edited by R. Phillips (BOA Editions, ), 1992
      - Introduction (Box 22)
      - Holograph ms. (Box 22)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 22)
      - Typescript ms., page proofs; Notes - holograph ms. (Box 22)
      - Notes for early version of Introduction (Box 22)
      - Typescript, copyedited, 3 folders (Box 22)
      - Production records
        - Page proofs, corrected, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Page proofs, corrected, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Triumph of the Night (Carroll & Graf), 1989
      - Introduction, typescript ms. (Box 23)
    - Welch, Denton. The Stories of Denton Welch / edited by R. Phillips (Dutton, ), 1985
      - Table of Contents, Preface, typescript ms. (Box 23)
      - Typescript ms. of unpublished stories, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - William Goyen (Twayne), 1979
      - Chronology, typescript ms. (Box 23)
      - Appendix: Interview with W. Goyen, typescript ms. (Box 23)
      - Typescript ms., 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Typescript ms., 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Production records
        - Galleys (with Goyen additions, substitutions, corrections) (Box 23)
        - Galleys (Box 23)
    - Zaturenska, Marya. New Selected Poems by Marya Zaturenska, edited by R. Phillips (Syracuse University Press, ), 2002
      - "Marya Zaturenska's Depression Diary", 1933-1935; ms. by Mary Beth Hinton, copyedited by R. Phillips (Box 23A)
      - "For Bob Phillips from MBH ", 7/12/99 (Box 23A)
      - Personal note and Introduction by Patrick Gregory (Box 23A)
      - Front matter, Introduction, ms., copyedited (Box 23A)
      - Front matter, Introduction, ms., corrected (Box 23A)
      - Manuscript (Box 23A)
      - Production records (Box 23A)
  - Essays
    - "A+ for C- Owen", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Academics: a Rant", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Amherst Poets", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Amy Jones, Artist, Meets Marianne Moore, Poet", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Are Those Real Poems, or Did You Write Them Yourself?", typescript ms., galleys; See also "Some Readings on Readings" (Box 24)
    - "The Artist and the Introvert: Nigel Dennis' A House in Order", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Beauty Out of Anxiety: Memories of John Logan", ms. revisions; See also "Remembering John Logan" (Box 24)
    - "The Bleeding Rose and the Blooming Mouth: the Love Poems of Anne
      - Holograph ms. (Box 24)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "The Bookman Inside the Gates", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Brave and Cruel: the Short Stories of Denton Welch", Studies in Short Fiction (Box 24)
    - "Breaking Down 'Breakdown Lane'", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "The Burning Ground" (collection), typescript ms.; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - "Cal & Jean, Randall & Oranges: Some Letters of Delmore Schwartz"
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24)
      - Production records (Box 24)
    - "Carson McCullers: a Selected Checklist", 1956-1964; typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Celebration with Signatures", typescript draft, revisions (Box 24)
    - "The Curtains Look Too Jewish, or My Years in Advertising", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "The Dark Funnel: a Reading of Sylvia Plath"
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24)
      - Modern Poetry Studies, v. 3, no. 2, 1972 (Box 24)
    - "Death and Resurrection: Tradition in Thomas' 'After the Funeral'", McNeese Review (Box 24)
    - "Delmore Schwartz: Letters to Allen Tate", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Delmore Schwartz: Toward Reassessment", holograph and typescript mss. (Box 24)
    - "DeLoss & the Found", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "The Democracy of Universal Vulnerability: the Poetry of Isabella Gardner"
      - Holograph ms. (Box 24)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Dinesen's 'Monkey' and McCuller's 'Ballad': a Study in Literary Affinity", Studies in Short Fiction (Box 24)
    - "'Eliot's Anti-Semitism' by Delmore Schwartz, notes by Robert Phillips", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "An Encyclopedia of My Dead"
      - Holograph ms. (Box 24)
      - Typescript ms., 4 folders (Box 24)
    - "Even Here ...: Notes on Robert Francis", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Exalted Times: William Goyen's Poems", typescript mss. (Box 24)
    - "Farrell's Progress: Innovation in the Later Fiction", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Featured Poet: Horace Gregory"
      - Holograph ms. (Box 24)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24)
      - Poetry Pilot, Apr. 1991 (Box 24)
    - "Finding, Losing, Expressing, Reclaiming, Turning: an Afterword on Why I Write Poems"
      - Holograph ms. (Box 24)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Fitzgerald and West's Day of the Locust, typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "For George Plimpton's Oral History of Truman Capote", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Freaking Out: the Short Stories of Carson McCullers", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "A Game of Catch"
      - Typescript ms. draft (Box 24)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Goodbye to the Bow Tie", holograph ms. (Box 24)
    - "Gore Vidal's Greek Revival: 'The Ladies in the Library'", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "The Gothic Architecture of The Member of the Wedding", winter 1964; Renascence (Box 24)
    - "In Youth Is Pleasure: Symbol and Symbolic Acts", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Introduction to 'Portrait of a City: Syracuse, the Old Home Town'" / by John A. Williams, holograph, typescript mss. (Box 24)
    - "James T. Farrell at Seventy", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "The Joy of Texts", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Jump-Starting Poetry", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Karl Shapiro and His Latest Poems", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Larger Than Life: Mythology and Carolyn Kizer", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Letters to a Young Writer - Delmore Schwartz", typescript draft (Box 24)
    - "Letters to R. P. Blackmur, - Delmore Schwartz" (began as: Delmore Schwartz: Letters to R. P. Blackmur), 1936-1946; typescript ms.; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - "Mask and Symbol in Set This House on Fire, typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Monomyth in Denton Welch's Maiden Voyage", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Nathanael West's Derivative Genius: The Day of the Locust and Sherwood Anderson", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Note on 'An Argument in 1934', holograph, typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Notes on Branches" (by Mitch Cullin), holograph, typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - On Not Being (Particularly) Well-Hung", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "On Not Knowing What One Has Written"
      - Holograph ms. (Box 24)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "On Signing Books & Book Signing", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "An Open Letter to James Dickey", holograph, typescript mss. (Box 24)
    - [Philip Booth's] "Death Sentences"
      - Holograph ms. (Box 24)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Philosophical and Aesthetic Implications of the Imagist Creed", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Poetry Chronicle: Some Versions of the Pastoral"
      - Holograph ms. (Box 24)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Poetry, Prosody, and Meta-Poetics: Karl Shapiro's Self-Reflexive Poetry", holograph, typescript mss.; See also Writings: Miscellaneous: Tapes (Box 29) (Box 24)
    - "The Quest for the Unattainable: John Logan's Anonymous Lovers", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "The Quick-Change Artist: Notes on Horace Gregory's Poetic Imagery", typescript ms. (Box 24)
    - "Remembering John Logan", holograph ms.; See also "Beauty Out of Anxiety: Memories of John Logan" (Box 24A)
    - "The Romance of Prophecy: Goyen's In a Farther Country"
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24A)
      - Southwest Review (Box 24A)
    - "Samuels and Samson: Theme and Legend in 'The White Rooster'", typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - "Selected Letters of Delmore Schwartz and James Laughlin" (selected and edited by R. Phillips for The Paris Review article)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24A)
      - Production records (Box 24A)
      - Production records, with Laughlin's annotations (Box 24A)
    - Shapiro, Karl. Essay on Rhyme Afterword
      - "First version", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 24A)
      - "Revisions", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - "Shirley Jackson", typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - "Some Notes on Painting-Poems"
      - Holograph ms. (Box 24A)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - "Some Readings on Readings", holograph, typescript mss.; See also: "Are Those Real Poems, or Did You Write Them Yourself?" (Box 24A)
    - "Sweet Potato Memories", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - "Symbols and Burlesque in Carson McCullers' The Ballad of the Sad Cafe", typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - "The Theme of Spiritual Isolation in Farrell's 'Danny O'Neill Petalogy'", typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - "The Third Biggest Observance", typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - "To Be Oneself: Some Letters by William Goyen" (selected and annotated by R. Phillips), typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - "Visiting the Gregorys"
      - Notes on Marya Zaturenska, holograph ms. (Box 24A)
      - Holograph ms. (Box 24A)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - "A Voice Through a Cloud: Denton Welch's Ultimate Voyage"
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24A)
      - The Centennial Review, spring 1971 (Box 24A)
    - "A Way of Life: Some Letters by William Goyen" (selected and annotated by R. Phillips)
      - Typescript mss., 2 folders (Box 24A)
    - "Why I Write", typescript ms.; 2 folders (Box 24A)
    - "William Goyen: Selected Letters" (proposal submitted to The Paris Review)
      - Typescript ms. (Box 24A)
      - Holograph ms. (Box 24A)
    - "The Writings of William Van O'Connor, 1937-1965", typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - "You're Not Getting Older, You're Getting Better: Notes on Aging and Writing", typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - Untitled (re: Shirley Jackson) (Box 24A)
  - Interviews
    - Goyen, William, typescript ms.; See also Writings: Miscellaneous: Tapes (Box 29); 2 folders (Box 24A)
    - Larkin, Philip, typescript ms.; 2 folders (Box 24A)
    - Laughlin, James, See also Writings: Miscellaneous: Tapes (Box 29) (Box 24A)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, typescript ms. (Box 24A)
    - Shapiro, Karl Jay, typescript ms.; See also Writings: Miscellaneous: Tapes (Box 29); 3 folders (Box 24A)
    - Smith, William Jay, See also Writings: Miscellaneous: Tapes (Box 29); 5 folders (Box 24A)
    - Spencer, Elizabeth, typescript ms.; 5 folders (Box 25)
    - Styron, William, typescript ms.; 3 folders (Box 25)
    - Zaturenska, Marya, typescript ms.; 3 folders (Box 25)
  - Novels
    - "Below the Line", typescript ms.; 4 folders (Box 25)
    - "Fallick: a Fiction", typescript ms. (Box 25)
    - "The Glass Garden"
      - Typescript ms., 3 folders (Box 25)
      - Epilogue, typescript ms. (Box 25)
      - Typescript ms., 3 folders (Box 25)
      - Typescript ms., 4 folders (Box 25)
    - "Her Father's House", typescript ms.; 5 folders (Box 26)
    - "Home Movies", typescript ms.; 3 folders (Box 26)
    - "Rite of Spring", typescript ms.; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Poetry
    - By title (A-K), 12 folders (Box 26)
    - By title (L-Z), 5 folders (Box 26A)
    - "Eight Pages of Poetry in Support of an Application to Read in the Winter/Spring 1987 'Open Voice Awards'", typescript ms. (Box 26A)
    - "Eight Poems from Personal Effects", typescript ms. (Box 26A)
    - "Hard Labor" (collection), typescript ms. (Box 26A)
    - "Miss Crustacean" (collection), typescript ms. (Box 26A)
    - "Nine Poems, 1981-1986", typescript ms. (Box 26A)
    - "Ten Poems, 1989-91", typescript ms. (Box 26A)
    - "Thirteen Poems, 1989-90", typescript ms. (Box 26A)
  - Reviews
    - By author A-Z, 7 folders (Box 27)
    - Multiple authors, 4 folders (Box 27)
  - Scripts
    - "Bobby Shaftoe", typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "Circumstances", typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "A House on Plum Street", typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "I Have Played a Trick on You", typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "Let's Do It" (alternate title: "The Joc Doc"), holograph ms. (Box 27)
    - "Raymond Carver Play Adaptations", manuscript (Box 27)
    - "A Sentimental Education" (alternate title: "The Secret Cover"), holograph ms. (Box 27)
    - "A Teacher's Reward", typescript ms. (Box 27)
  - Speeches
    - Introductions, 7 folders (Box 27)
    - "Andy Jenkins, R.I.P." [eulogy], Dec. 1994; holograph, typescript mss. (Box 27)
    - "Beating the Bushes: Karl Shapiro and the Prairie Schooner", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "Creative Writing in the English Department", typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "D[elta] U[psilon] Initiation, University of Houston, Jan. 9, 1995", typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "How Poets Earn a Living" - Wesleyan Writers' Conference, typescript mss. (Box 27)
    - "How to Read Fiction, Or the Story-teller's Art" - The Menil Collection, Oct. 26, 1995; ms. (Box 27)
    - "In a Farther Country: Goyen's Novel of Ecology & Magical Realism" -American Studies Association of Texas, Nov. 1998; typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "The Magic of Manuscripts" - Syracuse University Library Associates, Sept. 2000; holograph, typescript (Box 27)
    - "The Ming Vase of Poetry Reading Series': 25 Years at the Katonah Village Library", holograph ms.; See also Writings: Miscellaneous: Tapes (Box 29) (Box 27)
    - "National Book Award presentation" - Plaza Hotel, New York City, Nov. 15, 1995; holograph, typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "Notes of a Native Son in Prose & Poetry", typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "The Poets' Prize", Mar. 7, 1997; typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "The Poets' Prize", May 18, 2000; typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "Richard M. Nixon, Billy Graham, & Mr. Whipple", Oct. 2000; Whiting Foundation address (Box 27)
    - "Serendipity and [Delmore] Schwartz" - Syracuse University Library Associates, Nov. 13, 1986; typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "Stages in Writing & Publishing" - Houston Women's Writers' Group, June 1994 (Box 27)
    - "The State of American Poetry Today", typescript and holograph mss. (Box 27)
    - "A Swarm of Bees: Personal Experiences Behind Aspects of Alice" - Lewis Carroll Society of North America, May 8, 1999; holograph, typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "Toast" to William Pearson Tolley on the occasion of his 90th birthday celebration, ms. (Box 27)
    - "The Value of Poetry Readings", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "What's Happening in American Fiction?", typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - "Why I Write" - TICW Conference, Feb. 1, 1996; holograph, typescript ms. (Box 27)
    - Untitled (Box 27)
  - Stories
    - "Adam and Steve", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "After the Train", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Afternoon of the Summer", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "All Day the Mountain", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "And This Little Piggy Had None", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "The Angel of the Church", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Ashes to Ashes", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Auslanders", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "The Back of the Bus", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Barry Peckerman", holograph ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Bashing in the 'Burbs", holograph ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Bashing in the 'Burbs", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "A Biological Accident", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "The Birthday Tree", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "The Bonding", holograph and typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "A Brief Encounter", holograph ms. (Box 27A)
    - "A Brilliant Career", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "The Capitals of the World", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "The Cat Who Practiced Yoga", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Children of Old Booger", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Chrysanthemums in the Fall", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Cold Blood", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "The Cutting", typescript ms.; 3 folders (Box 27A)
    - "Dandelions and Goldenrod", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "The Daughter", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "A Day in the Life", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Dead Ringer", typescript ms.; 4 folders (Box 27A)
    - "The Death of a Good Man", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "The Ding Wing", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Dome of Many-Colored Glass", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Dress Code", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Ed McMahon, Dick Clark, the Camera Man, and the Balloon Man", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Failures", holograph ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Fallick", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Fallick: a Fragment", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Fallick: Two Fragments", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Fallick Ascends to Heaven", holograph, typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Fallick Blacks Out", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "Fallick Rides Again", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "False Blue", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "The Fay Wray Memorial Day Party"
      - Holograph ms. (Box 27A)
      - Typescript ms. with holograph corrections, 3 folders (Box 27A)
    - "Figure in a Chair", typescript ms. (Box 27A)
    - "First Prelude to Nothing", typescript ms. (Box 27A)